cichlid-forum.com 2010-06-25

# Cichlid-Forum.com - Privacy Policy

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Cichlid-Forum, ( _CF_ ). The following discloses our Privacy Policy.  
  
---  
What Information We Gather and Track  
  
_Personal Information_

We request personal information when you register as a member of this site, any time you submit materials to be used and/or displayed on this Web site, subscribe to our newsletter, correspond with us or engage in certain other activities on our Web site. For example: 

  1. When you register, we ask you to supply an accurate email address and to specify your geographical location. You may chose, however, to hide your email address from the public, in which case it is held in the strictest of confidence. Your location does not have to be specific, but is requested in an effort to help members become better acquainted. 
  2. If you submit a photograph for use in the gallery, the author's name is requested. This is to ensure the author credit and that they retain all copyright privileges as well as to protect _CF_ in case of fraudulent misrepresentation.  

You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction or participate in the activity.  
  
_Cookies_

When you register as a member of _CF_ , our Web server will send a "cookie" to your computer. A [cookie](http://webopedia.internet.com/TERM/c/cookie.html) is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk nor read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to recognize you when you are logged into the _CF_ Web site; thereby allowing you personalize your settings and to provide you with information and services that are tailored to you as an individual. For example, cookies record your user name so that you can be automatically logged in to the Web site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.   
  
_IP Adresses_

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the _CF_ Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the _CF_ Network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement.  
  
How We Use The Information We Gather and Track  
  
We use personally identifiable information in the following ways:

  1. To permit you to participate in the forum, and prevent other users from tampering with your posts, comments, or personalized sections; 
  2. To protect any submitted material that belongs to you; 
  3. To provide you with informational updates pertaining to the Web site; 
  4. To record your user name to allow you to automatically get logged in when accessing the site; 
  5. To allow you to participate in the various contests offered by _CF_ ; 
  6. To permit others to see your presence at the Web site.  

With Whom We May Share Your Information  
  
Any and all information you willingly disclose to _CF_ is held strictly confidential. **We will not sell any personally identifying information** obtained through this Web site to any other organization, and we will never willfully disclose any personal identification information about our audience to any third party.
